Brandon LaFoy BSN RN

824 DeSoto Drive • Desoto, TX 75115 Phone: 712-304-0741 • E-Mail: blafoy076@yahoo.com

Professional Summary

I am BSN RN prepared nurse seeking a challenging and rewarding career as RN in the ED. I am an ED Nurse with over 7 years experience working in Emergency care and in high patient volume settings. Additional experience in Charge role, telemetry, neuro-telemetry, neuro-surgical, heart failure, and long term care areas for a total of 11 plus years nursing experience.

Licenses/Certifications

- Registered Nurse in the state of Iowa, License number 123086
- Registered Nurse in the state of New York, License number 715205, Certificate number 9349131
- Basic Life Support (BLS) Certification 2016-2018
- Advanced cardiac life support 2015-2017 & Pediatric Life Support (PALS) Certification 2015-2017
- TNCC Trauma Nurse Core Course 2015-2019

Professional Experience

- Methodist Dallas Medical Center Dallas, TX | ED RN/Staff Nurse (2/12/18-Current)
- Methodist Dallas Medical Center Dallas, TX | ED RN/Travel Nurse (8/21/17-11/18/17)
- Weill Cornell Medical Center Manhattan, NY | ED RN/Travel Nurse (3/06/17-07/15/17)
- St. Luke's Mount Sinai Manhattan, NY | ED RN/Travel Nurse (11/16/16-2/10/17)
- Weill Cornell Medical Center Manhattan, NY | ED RN/Travel Nurse (8/22/16-11/19/16)
- Mercy Medical Center Des Monies, IA | ED RN (October 2015-August 2016)
- Mercy Medical Center 9 South & 6 North Des Moines, IA | RN Staff Nurse (May 2012-October 2015)
- Audubon County Memorial Hospital Audubon, IA | LPN/RN Staff Nurse (02/2009-08/2013

Education and Training

- University of Texas at Arlington | Arlington TX | Bachelors of science | Nursing | May 2016
- Iowa Western Community College | Council Bluffs, IA | Associates of Science | Nursing | May 2009